Chang Li Toronto, Canada <u>LinkedIn</u> | <u>GitHub</u> | <u>lichang9488@gmail.com</u> | Mobile: 306-341-0537

FULL STACK DEVELOPER

I have 8 years of experience as a computer mechanic with a year of coding experience in JavaScript, Typescript, Python and Ruby. I am knowledgeable in both hardware and software, with a strong troubleshooting and communicating skill sets. I am a quick learner with passion for technology who is able to adapt in new environments.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Languages: JavaScript, Typescript, Ruby, Python, HTML, CSS

Frameworks: React.js, Express, Node.js, JQuery, Rails **Libraries**: Material UI, Bootstrap, Redux, React Router

Databases: MongoDB, PostgreSQL, Firebase

EXPERIENCE

Store ManagerFeb 2017 – Feb 2022Uniway Computer Solutions LTDSaskatoon, Saskatchewan

• Provided affordable laptops during Covid pandemic for kids doing online courses.

- High customer satisfaction rating with an average of 4.7 stars on Google Review.
- Led a team of 4 technicians to provide technical support for individuals, businesses and government

organizations.

Computer Mechanic

Uniway Computer Solutions LTD

Aug 2014 – Feb 2017 Saskatoon, Saskatchewan

- Troubleshooted hardware (e.g., replaced worn-out components with micro-soldering) and software (e.g., data recovery, remote control)
- Managed a computer repair shop as a senior computer mechanic, responsible for overseeing a team of 4 technicians and ensuring that all repairs were completed accurately and efficiently.

EDUCATION

LightHouse LabsDiploma in Full Stack Web Development

Online, Canada Jan 2023 – Apr 2023

University of Saskatchewan *BMSC in Microbiology and Immunology*

Saskatoon, Saskatchewan Sep 2010 – Aug 2014

PROJECTS

E-Clothing | React.is, Redux, Typescript, Firebase, Git | Source Code

July 2022 - Aug 2022

- Designed and developed a responsive e-commerce website with a user-friendly interface using HTML, CSS, and ReactJS and JavaScript
- Managing back end, authentication login and database with **Firebase**
- Built streamlined checkout process with Stripe API.

Natours | *Node.js, Express, JavaScript, Mapbox, Git* | <u>Source Code</u>

Oct 2022 - Dec 2022

- Developed a responsive single page App with ReactJS. Users could leave commits and ratings, with a secure authentication cookie sending JSON Web Token.
- A CRUD application exposed using a RESTful API made with Node.js. Exposed POST, GET, PATCH and DELETE HTTP methods using Express

<u>Interview Scheduler</u> | ReactJS, PostgreSQL, JavaScript, WebSocket, Git | <u>Source Code</u>

Feb 2022

- Interview Scheduler is a single page App that allows users to create, edit and delete scheduled interviews with candidates on **WebSocket** real-time without refreshing the page.
- The app uses modern web technologies such as React Hooks and Redux for state management, and Axios
 for making API calls to the server. Deployed front end on Netlify, back end on RailWay.